Guide to the Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records, 1942-2005.
Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records, 1942-2005
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Textiles and Apparel records, 1942-2005.
23/19/2807
New York State College of Human Ecology. Department of Textiles and Apparel
6.5 cubic ft.
Syllabi, reports, minutes, publications, and audiocasettes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Annual reports, faculty meeting minutes, department newsletters, committee minutes, and other papers of the department. Also, material on course syllabi, outlines and descriptions of exhibits; audio cassettes of talks.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Department was formed in 1985 upon the dividing of the Department of Design and Environmental Analysis into Textile and Apparel Department and Department of Interior Design, Planning and Management; Design and Environmental Analysis had evolved from the Department of Textile and Clothing, which was formed in 1925.
Department changed its name to Fiber Science and Apparel Design in the spring semester, 2007.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Annual reports, faculty meeting minutes, department newsletters, committee minutes, and other papers of the department; includes a history of the evolution of the department. Also, material on course syllabi, outlines and descriptions of exhibits, featuring Mary McFadden, and Jon Haggins; audiocassettes of talks by Mary Purchase and Anita Racine.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Haggins, Jon.; McFadden, Mary; Purchase, Mary E.(Mary Elizabeth), 1921-; Racine, Anita.
Subjects:
Textile fabrics--Study and teaching.; Textile schools--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Clothing and dress--Study and teaching.; Clothing trade--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design records #23-19-3780
See also New York State College of Home Economics records #23-2-749
See also New York State College of Human Ecology records #23-2-2817
SERIES LIST
Series I. Course Material
Box 3, folders 7-17
Series II. Exhibits
Box 3, folders 18-26, Box 4 folder 18
Series III. Meeting Minutes
Box 1, folders 14-23, 25-26
A. Faculty
B. Extension-TXA
C. Graduate Field-TXA
Series IV. Newsletters & Publications
Box 1, folders 27-30; Box 2 folders 10-20; Box 5; Box 6
A. Extension - TXA
B. Housing and Design
C. News from the Department of Textiles and Clothing
D. TXA News
E. Topstitch
F. TXA Publications
Series V. Reports
Box 1, folders 3, 8-17, 34; Box 2, folders 107
A. Annual
B. Extension - TXA
C. Faculty Annual Reports
D. Various Reports
Series VI. Subject Files
Box 1, folders 1-2, 4-7, 24, 31-33, Box 4 folders 1-11
Series VII. Audiocasette tapes
tr. 7767a and tr. 7768a
Series VIII. Projects and Proposal
Box 4 folders 12 - 17
Series IX. Graduate Programs
Box 5 folders 1 - 4, 11
Series X. Publicity
Box 5 folders 5 - 7
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Course Material
  - Course descriptions (TXA and DEA), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New course proposals in TXA, 1986-1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - TXA course syllabi (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - TXA course schedules, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Transfer, orientation, general TXA information (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - TXA/DEA 264 course information and slides, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - DEA 230, DEA, 232, DEA 240, DEA 330, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - DEA course information and syllabi, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - TXA/DEA 465 course outlines, Beate Ziegert, slides, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Course syllabi, DEA 335, 401, 436, 439, 600, 635, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Course and course enrollment--Peter Schwartz, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - TXA 146 - Functional Clothing, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - TXA 238 - Textiles for Interiors, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - TXA/DEA 235 - Intro to Textiles Science, 1983-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - TXA 235/238, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - TXA 241 - Assessment of Product Quality, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - TXA 245:Dress: A Reflection, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - TXA 269 - Style, Fashion and the United States Apparel Industry, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - TXA 275 - Photoshop for Portfolio Development, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - TXA 301 - Investigative Research on the Social Impact of Science, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - TXA 332 - Designers as Entrepreneurs, 2001-2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - TXA 336 - Fundamentals of Color and Dyeing, 1989, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - TXA 367 - Apparel Design III, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - TXA 337 - Structural Fabric Design, 1986-1996 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - TXA 368 - Computer Aided Apparel Design, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - TXA 370 - Principles of Color and Design in Textiles, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - TXA 375 - Visual Studies: Color and Surface Design of Textiles, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - TXA 405 - Organizations and Policies in the Federal System, 19910-1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - TXA 425 - Computer Aided Apparel Design, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - TXA 438 - Apparel Textiles, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - TXA 445 - Functional Clothing Design, 1979-1985 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - TXA 461 - Issues in Management and Marketing, 1987-1991 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - TXA 465 - Apparel Design: Product Development and Presentation, 1985-2002 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - TXA 446 - Intermediate Functional Clothing, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - TXA 620 - Physical Properties of Fiber-forming Polymers and Fibers, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - TXA 621 - Characterization of Fibrous Materials, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - TXA 626 - The Chemistry of Textiles Finishes and Dyeing, no date (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - TXA 631 - International Production and Trade, 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - TXA 635 - Special Topics, 1990-1999 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - TXA 639 - Mechanics of Fibrous Assemblies, 1987-2005 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - TXA 664 - Human Factors - Anthropometrics and Apparel, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - TXA/DEA 242 - Field Experience in New York City, 1981-1990 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - TXA/DEA 331 - Textile and Apparel Industry, 1984-2003 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - TXA/DEA 433 - Structure and Properties; DEA 436 - Textile Chemistry; DEA 438 - Textiles in Fashion and Function, 1980-1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - TXA/DEA 635 - Special Topics in Textiles, 1980, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - TXA/DEA 636 - Textile Chemistry, 1983-1990 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - TXA/DEA 639 - Mechanics of Fibrous Structures, 1982, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - TXA/DEA 637 - Frontiers in Textiles, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - MSE 620 - Synthesis of Polymeric Materials, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Interdisciplinary Course - Composite Materials, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - HE 100 - Critical Reading and Thinking, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Textiles and Clothing 110 - Synthetic Fibers and Plastics in Society, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Photographs of student designed work, field trips, classroom projects, department publicity and items from the costume collection, 1993 (Box 8)
    Photographs were originally in a binder
- Series II. Exhibits
  - TXA exhibits and display-slides, 1982; 1983,; 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American Clothing: Identity in Mass Culture exhibit--Beate Ziegert [1/3], 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - American Clothing: Identity in Mass Culture exhibit--Beate Ziebert [2/3], 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - American Clothing: Identity in Mass Culture exhibit--Beate Ziebert [3/3], 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - American Clothing: Identity in Mass Culture exhibit--Human Ecology Forum, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Spring
  - Apparel design exhibit, 1986; 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Jon Haggins: A designer and his dresses exhibit, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Mary McFadden, apparel design work exhibit, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ryozo Morishita exhibit, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Medieval legend exhibit--Niezelski/VanZile, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Workshop -CAD design, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Series III. Meeting Minutes
  - A. Faculty
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1985-08-1986-07 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1986-08-1987-07 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1987-08-1988-07 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1988-08-1989-07 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1989-08-1990-07 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1990-08-1991-07 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - TXA faculty meeting minutes, 1992-08-2006-07 (Box 7, Folder 1-14)
  - B. Extension-TXA
    - TXA extension minutes, 1986-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - C. Graduate Field-TXA
    - TXA graduate field minutes, 1986-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Series IV. Newsletters and Publications
  - A. Extension - TXA
    - Extension newsletter, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Extension newsletter, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Extension newsletter, 1953-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Extension newsletter, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Extension newsletter, 1960-1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - B. Housing and Design
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Housing and Design newsletter, 1955; 1959,; 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - C. News from the Department of Textiles and Clothing
    - News from the Department of Textiles and Clothing, 1956-05-1960-05 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - News from the Department of Textiles and Clothing, 1961-02-1969-04 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - D. TXA News
    - TXA News, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - TXA News, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - TXA News, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - TXA News, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - TXA News, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - TXA News, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - TXA News, 2002-2006 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - E. Topstitch
    - Newsletter--"Topstitch", 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - F. TXA Publications
    - 100 Topics for 4-H Clothing and Textiles, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 4-H Clothes Horse, 1976-1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 4-H Clothing Level 1 and 2 - Clues to Clothing, no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Closer Look at Fibers, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Fusing Revolution, no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A Guide for Clothing Revolution, no date (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Author: Lowry, Suzanne
    - A Guide to Clothing Construction, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A Guide to Fiber and Fabric Testing, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A New Flame Retardant Fiber, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A New View of Luxury, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A Personal Assessment for Starting a Business, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Gotwals, Lois
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Weaver, Elaine Knowles
    - A Small Wear Study of Boys' Flame Retardant Cotton Sleepware, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Stout, Evelyn
    - A Tally on Today's Threads, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness - Bicycle Wear, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Watkins, Susan and McLean, Jean
    - Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness - Choosing a Sport Bra, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Watkins, Susan
    - Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness - Socks, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness - Visibility, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Adapting Ready-To-Wear Garments for People in Wheelchairs, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Adapting Ready-To-Wear Garments for People with Arthritis, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Altering Garments for Lymphodimia, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Purcell, Marianne
    - Altering Ready-Mades, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Always Wear the Right Stuff, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Author: Coffman, Charlotte
    - Analyzing Fit, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Apron with Plastic Ring Band, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Articles of Clothing Chart, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Backpacks, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Blum, Madeline and Warner, Gret
    - Balancing Family Life with a Home-Based Business, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Barbecue Apron, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bargain Ideas for Storing Children's Clothing, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Woodard, Janice
    - Be a Label Detective, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Bonded Fabrics" - article, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bonded Fabrics - brochure, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Books for Young People on the Disabled, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Boots, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Blum, Madeline
    - Boots for Walking and Hiking, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Border Prints, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bound Bottonholes, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Business Plan Guidelines, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Rice, Frederick
    - Business Use of Your Car, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Owen, William
    - Button Loops, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Buy by Size, Not Age, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Buying by Size, Not Age, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Buyting by Size, Not Age, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Buying Clothes for Small Children, 1970 and 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Landry, Lenore
    - Buying Snowsuits, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Care, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Care of Down, Fiberfill and Needlepunch Insulation, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Caring for Rayon Isn't Easy, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Carpenter Apron, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Championship Material, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Chanle Binding, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Mclean, Jean
    - Change for your Dollar, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Changing Shape in Fashion, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Children's Flame-Retardant Sleepware, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Children's Shoes, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Elsworth, Billie
    - Choosing Becoming Colors, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cire, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cleaning Clothes Salvaged from Flooded Homes, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cleaning Quilts and Comforters, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Closet Economics, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Clothes for Jogging and Running, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Clothes Moths, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Klass, Carolyn
    - Clothes to Keep you Dry, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Clues to Quality, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Cooke, Mardee and West, Carol
    - ColtheSense - Design for Dressing, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Dressing to Keep Cool, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Atkin, Gret
    - ClotheSense - Dressing to Keep Warm, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Judging Fabric Quality, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Kauffeld, Karen
    - ClotheSense - Knit Picking, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Flatter Your Figure: Women, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Big and Beautiful, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ClotheSense - Renew and Recycle, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Author: Robinson, Karen
    - Clothing and Energy Crossword Puzzle, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Clothing Construction Program, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Author: Yarbrough, Francenia
    - Clothing for Children, no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Clothing Suggestions for Farming Hazards, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Involves the Arms, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Involves the Hands, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Involves the Lower Leg, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Involves the Lower Torso, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Involves the Neck, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Suggestions for People Whose Physical Handicap Invovles the Upper Torso, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing Tips Following a Mastectomy, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing-Related Community Service Ideas, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Clothing, Activity, and Comfort - for the leader and the member, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Articles about Bonded Fabrics, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Color in Fabrics, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Companies Producing Clothing and Shoes for Fitness, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Construction Techniques for Bonded Fabrics, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Construction Techniques for Knitted Fabrics, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Construction Techniques for Stretch Fabrics, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Construction Techniques for Vinyl Fabrics, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Construction Techniques on Today's Fabrics, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Consumer News Service - Clothing, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Questions and Answers About the Care Labeling Rule, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cool Weather Clothing Comfort for Boating and Fishing in New York State, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cording, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cotton - Fiber Facts, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cozy Lap Robe, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Crinkled Fabrics, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Current Concerns of the Textile Industry, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Author: Breen, Nancy
    - Dairy Goat Blanket, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Darts on Quilted Reversible Fabric, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Definitions of Computer Terms Used in the Apparel Industry, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - "Design Professor Puts Wasted Materials to Use" - article, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Developing a County Actionwear: Clothing for Fitness Program, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Directions for Shrinking Wool Fabrics, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Disabling Diseases and Conditions, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - District Training for Clothing Level II, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Author: Stout, Phyllis
    - Do Your Shopping by Cable TV, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Double Curve and Square Corner Exercise, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Author: Butzer, Jean
    - Drawstring Skirt, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Drawstring Tote Bag, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dress in a Winning Way - Slide Set Transcript, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dressing by Design, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dressing Children for Cold Weather, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dryclean Only - Consumer News Service, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Easy How's and Why's of Interfacing, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Easy Neck Placket, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Easy Wrap-Around Skirt, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Easy-to-Make Apron, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Educational Role of Extension in Home-Based Income Generation, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Author: Makela, Carole
    - Evaluation in the 4-H Clothing Program, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Fabric Clubs and Mail Order Houses, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabric Dictionary, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabric Facts Clippings, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabric Finishes Engineered for Serviceability, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Author: Blum, Madeline and Bogely, Carolyn
    - Fabric Finishes for Beauty, Service, Protection, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Author: Blum, Madeline; McFadden, Frances; McLean, Jean
    - Fabric Grain, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabric Horizons Swatch Feet, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabric Scavenger Hunt, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fabrics and Their Uses, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Factors Affecting Abrasion Resistance of Woven Fabrics, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Facts About Underfashions, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Author: McFadden, Frances and McLean, Jean
    - Facts, Questions, and Answers about Dyeing, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fake Leather and Vinyl, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Family Tips for Buying Today's Sewing Machines, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Federal Taxes, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Author: Passewitz, Gregory
    - Fiber and Fabric Resources, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fiber Facts, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fiber Properties, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fiber Trade Names, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Figure Flattery: Program Guide, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fitting and Pattern Alteration Teaching Guide, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Flammable Fabrics, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Author: Saltford, Nancy and Cook, Carolyn
    - Flammable Fabrics, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fly Opening--- Simplified Method, no date (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Focus on Fabrics, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Formaldehyde in Textiles, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Garments, "Recycling the Wardrobe" Kit, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Gauze Fabrics, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Getting Acquainted with Textiles, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Glossary of Financial Terms, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Author: Aubry, Janise
    - Glossary of Tailoring Terms, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Good Insulation Makes Warm Clothes, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Good News for Those Who Sew at Home, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Guide to the Let's Sew Projects, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Author: Hibben, Eleanor
    - Guidelines for Adapting Commercial Basic Skirt Patterns to Fit Black Women, no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Guidelines for Purchasing a Prosthesis After Mastectomy, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hand Finishing Details for a Tailored Garment, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Author: Reed, Janet
    - Handling Cloth: First Steps, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Author: Braise, Muriel
    - Handouts From " A Look at 4-H Clothing Construction Standards", no date (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - HBBRC: Some of the Options, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Helmets Required for Young Bike Passengers, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Author: Winter, Metta
    - Helping Youngsters Think About Evaluation, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hems, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Author: Blum, Madeline C.
    - His and Hers Poncho, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Home Based Business, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Author: Hogarth, Jeanne M.
    - Home-Based Business Bibliography, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How Do You Buy a T-Shirt?, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How Do You Buy Jeans?, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How Entrepreneurial Are You?, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How Fabrics Are Made, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to "Tune" a Sewing Machine to a Fabric, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Be Warm and Keep Your Fashion Cool, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How To Do a Market Survey, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Fit, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Insure Your Business, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Author: Stout, JaneAnn and Meek, James
    - How to Know Your Fabric Personalities, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Make a Reflective Vest, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How To Make a Wrist Pin Cushion, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Reline a Coat, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Author: Reed, Janet; Snellman, Adaline; Harrel, Gertrude
    - How to Separate the Professional From the Amateur Dressmaker, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Sew with Suede, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Sew…Stretch, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - How to Use a Basic Pattern, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Index to Alter Your Pattern, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Insulated Garments, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Insulation, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Interfacings, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - It's Paper, Sheet, Fabric; It's Spunbonded, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Jacket and Coat Hems, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Jiffy Lining, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)